instantscamalert.com 2018-10-18

# 

### Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy sets out how instantscamalert.com (ISA) uses and protects information that you give when you use this website.  
ISA is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be  
identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
ISA may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that   
you agree to changes.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we had put in  
place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect online. All the data giving  
by registered members will be used privately and won't be disclosed to any third parties. ISA is not responsible or liable for any   
loss of data which is caused by your or third-party - unpredictable faults.

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to   
enter your: name, username, e-mail address, e-wallet details if the registration is enabled.  
Such information may be used in one of the following ways:

1) To process transactions, for example RCB payments (referral commission back), buy/sell/trade internal shares.  
Your details whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason  
whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

2) To manage contests, promotions, surveys or similar actions.

3) To send newsletters by email. Currently this communication channel is not in use.

We implemented many security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter,  
submit, or access your personal information.

We use cookies (cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web  
browser (if you allow). Cookies recognize your browser and remember certain information. You can also allow to save your login   
details in your browser once you filled in any form at ISA, but this action is in your hands, just as like the security of stored  
details. We also use cookies to keep controll advertisements, referral links. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your   
details to third parties. We may use your details when we believe usage is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site   
policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, general information reagarding visitors, traffic may be  
provided to third parties for marketing, advertising purposes.

You agree that information, communications, materials discussed or availalble at ISA can't be taken as advice to invest.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us via our Support page.

All Rights Reserved. [instantscamalert.com](http://instantscamalert.com/) 2012-2016
